const Data = {
    target: {
        color: "rgb(39,174,96)",
        body: [
            {question: "What is Target Savings?", ans: "Target Savings allows you save towards multiple goals on your own or with groups"},
            {question: "Save with a group", ans: "You can save towards a common goal with friends and family. There are no limit to the number of savings group you can join"},
            {question: "Daily interest paid", ans: "Earn 10% per annum, paid daily into your wallet"}
        ]
    },
    safelock: {
        color: "rgb(34,149,242)",
        body: [
            {question: "What is Safelock?", ans: "Safelock allows you to set money aside for a fixed period of time without having access to it until maturity. IT's like having your own custom fixed deposit"},
            {question: "You're in control", ans: "Set the desired duration of time tolock funds. You can lock for as little as 10 days or as much as 1000 days"},
            {question: "Earn interest upfront", ans: "Up to 13% perannum, paid upfront"}
        ]
    },
    flexnaira: {
        color: "rgb(231,67,156)",
        body: [
            {question: "What is FlexNaira?", ans: "FlexNaira like a wallet system allows you stack up cash in Naira. Although, for now no features added for it"}
        ]
    },
    investify: {
        color: "purple",
        body: [
            {question: "How does Investify works?", ans: "Investify works like a normal investment platform. We display a wide range of verified investment opprtunities for you to pick and excel financially"},
            {question: "When do I get back my money?", ans: "Depends on you, the company you are investing in and the date of maturity of the investment. All these deternime how you can get back your money with or without profit"},
            {question: "Earn interest and dividends", ans: "Based on the performance of your investment, you can make a fortune and become rich overnight, lol"},
            {question: "Other questions?", ans: "Check the FAQs section of the investment you hope to buy"}
        ]
    }
}

export default Data;